Template Instantiation Commands for .NET Core CLI

Usage: new [options]

Options:
  -h, --help          Displays help for this command.
  -l, --list          Lists templates containing the specified name. If no name is specified, lists all templates.
  -n, --name          The name for the output being created. If no name is specified, the name of the current directory is used.
  -o, --output        Location to place the generated output.
  -i, --install       Installs a source or a template pack.
  -u, --uninstall     Uninstalls a source or a template pack.
  --type              Shows a subset of the available templates. Valid values are "project", "item" or "other".
  --force             Forces content to be generated even if it would change existing files.
  -lang, --language   Specifies the language of the template to create.


Class library (C#)
Author: Microsoft
Options:                                                                             
  -f|--framework  The target framework for the project.                              
                      netcoreapp2.0     - Target netcoreapp2.0                       
                      netstandard2.0    - Target netstandard2.0                      
                  Default: netstandard2.0                                            

  --no-restore    If specified, skips the automatic restore of the project on create.
                  bool - Optional                                                    
                  Default: false                                                     


