Template Instantiation Commands for .NET Core CLI

Usage: new [options]

Options:
  -h, --help          Displays help for this command.
  -l, --list          Lists templates containing the specified name. If no name is specified, lists all templates.
  -n, --name          The name for the output being created. If no name is specified, the name of the current directory is used.
  -o, --output        Location to place the generated output.
  -i, --install       Installs a source or a template pack.
  -u, --uninstall     Uninstalls a source or a template pack.
  --type              Shows a subset of the available templates. Valid values are "project", "item" or "other".
  --force             Forces content to be generated even if it would change existing files.
  -lang, --language   Specifies the language of the template to create.


Unit Test Project (C#)
Author: Microsoft
Options:                                                                                    
  -p|--enable-pack  Whether or not to enable packaging (via ("dotnet pack") for the project.
                    bool - Optional                                                         
                    Default: false                                                          

  --no-restore      If specified, skips the automatic restore of the project on create.     
                    bool - Optional                                                         
                    Default: false                                                          


